hello world for these thirty thirty
years ago when I started the book engine
future I feel so inspired I said oh we
have friends
otherwise we feel quite isolated that we
feel yeah I feel for me personally I
don't feel being a Buddhist living in
the heart
we need more relative belonging
doing meditation it's not uncivilized
but the whole society made us feel that
very uncivilized if you don't help
because you don't have televisions so
when we try to work on this thing
when Helen a book came out is such a
blessing if you all we have friends
which had the same frame of reference so
I just want to acknowledge yeah you know
great contribution you do for us and
it's not only asked because when we
translate will be published her books in
Burmese Burmese and feel the same
yes oh this is it so it helps other
people in other society feel that they
are not inferior so this kind of book is
very helpful and looking from the
Western perspective you see the value
here it helped us to look back at myself
as well so this is how we connect with
Helena I feel really close connection in
term of each have deep frame of
reference here for me myself I live here
for 10 years and try to use you know
what is p3 approach in this running this
ashram and Jane was with me for four
five years in this in this community
when we run we start the G ot cost then
she got sick and she had to come back to
Scotland so I have which spent half time
here ha
in Scotland luckily Jane also drawn to
the village and that's why I go there I
also have a chat with ya
what kind of eco village is happening in
the best so I bring some knowledge from
here which had that and then bring some
people who the appreciate here so the
choir enriching each other and you have
been teaching it